Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-101
  - Stanford materials
    - Artificial Intelligence (AI) Qualifying Exam, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee Asia/Pacific Research Center, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Aston University, 1987--1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - AT and T Grant, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Babbage Interview, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Boston Computer Museum, 1982--1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - John Seeley Brown--Notes on a conversation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - John Seeley Brown Nomination, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Budget Committee, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - The Center for Advanced Medical Informatics at Stanford (CAMIS), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Campbell Communications, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - B. Chandrasekaran, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - China--General, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Paul Cohen, 1987 -1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - CGL--Computer Graphics Labratory, 1988--1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Computer Science and Technology Board, 1987--1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Computerworld Smithsonian Awards, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Congressional Contacts, 1983--1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Consulting--Undersecretary of Defense, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Copyrights, Patents, 1980--1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Comprehensive Exams, 1987 -1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Sponsored Research Numbers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - DENDRAL Original, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Historical DENDRAL, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - DENDRAL--Conception, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - DENDRAL, 1985--1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - DOD Security Clearance, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Report of DOD and Defense Related Employment form, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Encyclopedia Americana, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Expert Systems (ES) with Applications: An International Journal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - EAF Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - EPAM, 1962--1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Expert Systems (ES) on Multi-Processor Arch: Results of Expiriments at the Heuristic Programming Project (HPP), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Ford Aerospace--Consulting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - John Fox, 1987--1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fujitsu, 1986--1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - EAF--Fanmail--General, 1984--1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Gannett Center for Media Studies--Columbia University, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Neil Grey--Rejoinder, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Grey, DENDRAL paper, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Paul Harmon--Forward, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Shozo Hibiko visit, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Heuristic Programming Project (HPP)--Presentation, Materials, Achievements, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Executive Committee, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Honda, 1987--1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - IAKE, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE), 1987--1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Intelligent Manufactoring Systems (Teicholz), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Peter Jackson, 1989--1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - International Technology Research Institute: International Technologies, Main Findings 1984--1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Knowledge Processing: From File Servers to Knowledge Servers, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL)--Kyoto, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Retreat, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Large Knowledge Bases (LKB), 1986--1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Large Knowledge Bases (LKB) / How Things Work (HTW)--Technical Background Materials, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Lawsuit / Rand Corporation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Large Multi-use Knowledge Bases, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - "Machines Who Think", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - MACSYMA Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation (MCC) / CYC West--Confidentiality Agreements, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation (MCC) - Contract Negotiations, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation (MCC), 1985--1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation (MCC) - University Affiliates, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corporation (MCC) - Legal, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - MOLGEN, 1980--1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Signal-to-Signal Transformation, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - The Art of Artificial Intelligence: Themes and Case Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Toward the Library of the Future, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - World Congress on Expert Systems (ES) Paper, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - On the Thresholds of Knowledge, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - On Generality and Problem Solving, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Encyclopedia Article, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - DENDRAL and META-DENDRAL--Journal of AI, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Knowledge Engineering: The Applied Side of Artificial Intelligence, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - DENDRAL and META-DENDRAL: Their Applications Dimension, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - EAF Reprints: Major Papers, 1977--1986 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - NASA Ames Agreement NCC 2-220, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - National Productivity Board, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) Proposal: Adaptive Intelligent Systems, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)--Digital Libraries, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1991--1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - NIH--DCRT Search Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - National Library of Medicine Board of Regents, Washington D.C., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - National Library of Medicine (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - National Library of Medicine (2 of 3), 1989--1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - National Library of Medicine (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - National Institute of health Site Visit, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - NEXT, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - NE Asia Forum, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - NTT Proposal, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Official Technology Assessment US Government, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Passport / Visas, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Liam Peyton's Thesis, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Liam Peyton Issue, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Feigenbaum, Personal, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Professor Pearl Pu, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Possible Publishers, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Regis McKenna--Productivity, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Random House, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Riplunch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Rockwell, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Koji Sasaki, 1989--1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Security Clearence--various, 1960--1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Retreat Slides, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Expert Systems (ES): Payoff and Pointers Cambridge, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Reasoning by Computer Using Knowledge Comp. Forum, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Expert Systems (ES): Payoff, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Space--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Space--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1982--1985 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Speech Systems, Inc., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Stefick, Mark, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Sumex, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Sumex, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Stanford, Consulting, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Stanford University Memo--Policies related to outside business activities, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Smart Valley, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Talks, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Technology Export, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Textroni, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Thank You Letters--General, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Texas Instruments Book Permission, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Texas Instruments Expert Systems (ES) Tools, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Traub, Joe, 1991--1993 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Trilogy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Universal General Proposal, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - U.S.C. Security Debriefing, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Van Nostrand Reinhold Comp. Inc., 1989 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Waterman, Gloria / Don, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Waterman Library--Dedication, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Westinghouse, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - "What Hath Simon Wrought" CMU--Letter of Agreement, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - White House Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - John Wiley and Sons, Publishers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Yusko thesis, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Feigenbaum Regret Letters, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Feigenbaum Invitation Regrets, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - EAF Expenses, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Expense Reciepts, Processed, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Expense Stuff, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - EAF's Expense Reinbursment, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - EAF's Petty Cash Reinbursment, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Petty Cash Forms, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - EAF's Book--Avron Barr, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - United Airlines, Mileage Plus, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Visitors--Regrets, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD)--PHD Admissions, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD)--Faculty Meetings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) /AI Agendas / Topics, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Faculty Meetings, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Faculty Meetings, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Defense Science Board, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - History 650, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hitachi Hyoron (preface), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - India Trip (trip cancelled), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - The Information Institute, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Information Technical Services, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Institute for Scientific Information, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Invitations, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Kodansha, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - National Academy of Science Research Panel AI and Cognitive Science EAF, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - NEXT Magazines Translations, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Swedish Academy of Sciences, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Centennial, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Stanford Class Schedule, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Stanford University Developement Office, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - North-East Asia Forum, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - CS 121 Professor Donald Mitchie, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Computer Models of Thought Learning and Skill, D. Mitchie, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - CS 121 Winter Quarter, 1990--191 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Academic Senate, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Class Lists, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Class Lists, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Students Grades, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Class List (Liam Peyton), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Student List, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Class Lists, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Class Lists, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Classes 1st Quarter, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Buchanan, Bruce G., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Stanford files "People"
      - Stanford files "People"--Bingaman, Jeff--Senate, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Stanford files "People"--Caddes, Carolyn--Silicon Valley Portraits, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Stanford files "People"--Cohen, Harold, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Stanford files "People"--Cohen, Paul, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Stanford files "People"--Confrey, Tony, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Stanford files "People"--Cornelius, Craig, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Stanford files "People"--Cushman, General John H., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Stanford files "People"--Djerassi, Carl, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Stanford files "People"--Fehling, Michael, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Stanford files "People"--Friiedland, Peter, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Stanford files "People"--Gabriel, Dick, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Stanford files "People"--Gupta, Rajiv--Application, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Stanford files "People"--Gupta, Anoop, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Stanford files "People"--Imai, Ken-ichi, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Stanford files "People"--Iwasaki, Yumi, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Stanford files "People"--Jobs, Steven, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kartam, Nabil, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kora, Sam, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kahn, Robert, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kanade, Takeo, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Stanford files "People"--Karp, Peter, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kay, Allen, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kempf, Renate, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kennedy, Donald, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kollmorgan, Lelland (Admiral), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Stanford files "People"--Kunz, John, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Stanford files "People"--Maegawa, Hirotoshi, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Stanford files "People"--McCarthy, John, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Stanford files "People"--Rice, James P., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Stanford files "People"--Rozenholc, Mrs. Maia, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Stanford files "People"--Rozenholc, Michel, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Stanford files "People"--Wallace, David, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Stanford files "People"--Wogrin, Nancy--MSAI, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Stanford files "People"--Wilson, Pete--Congress, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Stanford files "People"--Yamada, Hisao--Visit, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Stanford files "People"--Zschau, EAF--Congress, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Lu, Dr. Ruqian--Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Visitor, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Originals of Articles--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Originals--Forms--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Originals of Articles--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1983--1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Originals--Text--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1983--1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Originals--Articles--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1982--1986 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Cine--Beijing--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Anne Feibelman--Movie (HPP)--Selling, Advertising, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Movie--Distrubution--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985--1986 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Cine Film Award Ceremony--Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Film --Anne feibelman Trip, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL)--Exec--Movie--MSS, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Movie Scripts--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - World's Fair--Movie--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Movie--Showing--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Movie--Orders--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Movie--Stuff--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1984--1986 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Films--Computer Graphics--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Films--General--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Movie--Cine Award--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Report Distribution, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Info Packet, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Computer Science Department (CSD) Staff Meeting, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Visitors Day--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Display Case--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - High Tech Adv. Committee--Congressman Pete Wilson--Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Associates, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Software: MIT and JIPDEC Doc.s, 1989--1993 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Stanford Japan Center, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Japan Interviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Company Information, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Future of Computer Industry, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Research Seminar Materials, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Research Seminar Materials, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Japan / SW Final Papers of Seminar, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - SCTI-93 General Research Seminar, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SCTI-SJC Tymnet Access, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Computer Industry Project (CIP) Talk Revised, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Newell Speech, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Docs, 1983--1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Science Paper Due, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Science Chicago Talk, DENDRAL, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - AAAS Science Paper, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Defense Science Board, Summer Study, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cohen / Grinberg Paper, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - CS 123 (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - CS 123 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Draft Reports, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - CS 123--Spring, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Knowledge Processing: From File Servers to Knowledge Servers, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Papers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986- 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Misc. Interoffice correspondence, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Expert Systems (ES) Ideas, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Misc. Stanford Papers and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Misc. Papers, Journals, Articles ("Heap" ?), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Project Eurisko, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Slides (EAF's Talks), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Slides (EAF's Talks), 1987 and undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Slides--Netherlands (EAF's Talks), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Computer Forum (EAF's Talks), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Various Well-Tried Materials and Quotes for Knowledge Systems Lectures (EAF's Talks), 1983--1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - EAF's Slides (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day (EAF's Talks), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Large Multi-use Knowledge Bases Slides (EAF's Talks), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Large Multi-use Knowledge Bases Slides--IBM talk (EAF's Talks), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - How Things Work (HTW) Project Slides (EAF's Talks), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - How Things Work (HTW) Project Slides (Spring) (EAF's Talks), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Slides / Knowledge / Toward the Future (EAF's Talks), 1988--1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Slides / Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Overview of KSL, HTW, Engineer's Associate and MADE, KASE, BB (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Speaking--Advice, Organizations (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Fujitsu Forum Talk (EAF's Talks), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Feigenbaum Medal--World Congress on Expert Systems--Speech (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "Knowledge Talk"--view graphs (EAF's Talks), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - CYC Slides (EAF's Talks), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Knowledge Talks Materials (EAF's Talks), 1989--1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "Knowledge Talk" Supporting Materials (EAF's Talks), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Knowledge Talk" Supporting Materials (EAF's Talks), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - UCLA Talk (EAF's Talks), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Large Knowledge Bases (LKB) / Enterprise Integration (EAF's Talks), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Vision of Very Large Knowledge Bases (VLKB) (EAF's Talks), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Security Forum (EAF's Talks), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Knowledge Base and Knowledge Representation Research: Overview Viewgraphs (EAF's Talks), undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Transparencies (EAF's Talks), 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Dilbert for Talks (EAF's Talks), undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - UCLA Marschak Memorial (EAF's Talks), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Turing Award Speech (EAF's Talks), 1980 -1995 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Heuristic Programming Project (HPP) Reunion (EAF's Talks), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Possible Talk / Article based on 1992 Singapore (EAF's Talks) (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Feigenbaum Medal Winner--World Congress on Expert Systems--Lotfi Zadeh, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Blackboard--Historical, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Infrastructure Protection Initiative--Misc., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - EAF's Congressional Testimony, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Intraspect Folder, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Great Debates--within and about Artificial Intelligence (AI), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Modeling Techniques and Algorithms for Probalistic Model-based Diagnosis and Repair, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Computer History Museum, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Industry Publications, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Academic Papers (Not Feigenbaum's), 1996--2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Articles, 1998--2003 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Corespondence, 1991--2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Report on Future of Stanford Japan Center Research, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Associations, 198--2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Info Fusion, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Okawa, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Information Science Institute (ISI), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Cognitive Systems, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - NEC USA, Inc. Folder, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Cognitive Systems Workshop Folder, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - EAF's other Work and Stanford Office Stuff, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Bell, Gordon letter about Applied Artificial Intelligence (AI), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Donald Michie Articles, 1994--2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Calendar, 1998--1999 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Information Fusion Workshop, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Students Rate EAF, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Barr--Computer Industry Project, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Michael Reiter, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Stanford Computer Forum--Annual Meeting Binder, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Tour of SUMMIT Lab Folder, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - ICES Keynote Talk--Mexico City, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Robots, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Biographical Memoirs--H. Simon, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Emerging Draft, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Knowledge Management Materials--Misc "Course Notes", 1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Academic Papers and Speeches (not Feigenbaum's), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)